frontier.com 2016-06-02

# 

                                                                                                                     www.Frontier.com
Frontier Privacy Policy
Frontier is sensitive to privacy issues with respect to the use of identifiable customer information provided to us over
the Internet. We believe it is important for you to know how we handle the information about you that is received by
us when you visit. Online privacy focuses mainly on the protection of "customer identifiable" information (e.g.
personal information like your name, address, telephone number, email address, etc.) that an individual expects to be
kept private.
Collection of Personal Information
Except as provided below, we do not collect and then sell, distribute, or exchange personal information with third
parties. In order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"), Frontier does not knowingly
collect any information from children under 13.
Frontier uses common web site analysis software to monitor our site activity (e.g. number of visits, average time
spent on the site, number of page views, methods by which the site was found). We use this information internally
and with our advertisers to better understand our audience, offer more appealing content and continuously improve
the user experience. Frontier may make use of a technology called cookies, in order to provide you with customized
information for your specific market and to streamline and improve your user experience.
A cookie is a tiny element of data that a web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your hard
drive so we can recognize you when you return. We do not use this cookie to collect any personal information about
you or your family.
Some of the information found on a Frontier web site may be provided and managed by our partners and associates.
There may be instances where personal information that is entered is used by one of our content providers. In these
cases, that information is subject to the privacy policy of that provider. This Frontier web site may contain links to
other sites. While we try to link only to sites that share our high standards and respect for privacy, we are not
responsible for the content or the privacy practices employed by other sites.
Sharing Information
Frontier only shares personal information with unaffiliated organizations that perform services on our behalf and only
as necessary for them to perform these services. Frontier requires unaffiliated organizations to protect your personal
information consistent with this policy.
Frontier allows third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use
information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to our and other
websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more
information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies,
you can visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
Notification of Changes
Frontier reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and will post any revisions on this site.
Use of Content
You may use, copy and distribute the materials found on this Frontier web site for personal, noncommercial,
informational purposes only. All copies that you make of the material must bear any copyright, trademark or other
proprietary notice located on the site that pertain to the material being copied.

Accepting Cookies
You can order your browser to accept all cookies or to alert you every time a cookie is offered. Then you can decide
whether to accept one or not.
Do Not Call Policy
To view our Do Not Call Policy in it's entirety, click here.
